Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- W, 11535
  - Wilcken, Henry J., undated; cuid2372; 11616 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wilcox, George L. (1915-2002), 1953; cuid2373; 11617 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wildermuth, Gordon, 1976; cuid2374; 11618 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Williams, Blair, undated; cuid2375; 11619 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Williams, Dennis C., undated; cuid2376; 11620 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Williams, Frank H., 1961; cuid2377; 11621 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Williams, Robert P., Lieutenant, 1952; cuid2378; 11728 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Willig, George H., 1977; cuid2379; 11622 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wilson, Robert E., 1940; cuid2380; 11623 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Winkert, John W., circa 1951; cuid2381; 11624 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Winsche, Warren, 1939; cuid2382; 11625 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Winters, Warrinton, undated; cuid2383; 11626 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Wishert, John C., Major, 1954; cuid2384; 11627 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Wishnick, William, undated; cuid2385; 11628 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Witryk, Ted, 1999; cuid2386; 11629 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Witt, Christopher J., undated; cuid2387; 11630 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Witte, Arnold, undated; cuid2388; 11631 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Wojan, Clifford, undated; cuid2389; 11632 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Wolf, Barry, 1978; cuid2390; 11633 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Wolf, Edward L., undated; cuid2391; 11634 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Wolfe, Don M., undated; cuid2392; 11635 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Wolfgang, 1954; cuid2393; 11636 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Woll, William K., 1966; cuid2394; 11637 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Wong, Edward K. "Ted", undated; cuid2395; 11638 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Wonsicki, Edward A., Jr., 1959; cuid2396; 11639 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Wotherspoon, Neil, undated; cuid2397; 11640 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Wovomestko, Frederick, undated; cuid2398; 11641 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Wright, Chilton A., undated; cuid2399; 11642 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Wuestefeld, [Richard ?], undated; cuid2400; 11643 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Wulff, [Raymond ?], undated; cuid2401; 11644 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wulfken, Howard J., 1953, 1961; cuid2402; 11645 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Wunsch, Joseph W., 1959, 1965; cuid2403; 11646 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Wunsch, Elsie and Martin, 1996; cuid2404; 11647 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Wunsch, Samuel, 1958, 1967; cuid2405; 11648 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Y, 11649
  - Yang, Deane, undated; cuid2406; 11650 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Yang, Yisong, undated; cuid2407; 11651 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Yanis, Edward M., undated; cuid2408; 11652 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Yates, Chauncey V., Jr., undated; cuid2409; 11653 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Yates, Janet, undated; cuid2410; 11654 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Yeoman, Neil, 1955; cuid2411; 11655 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Ying, Nelson, 1997; cuid2412; 11656 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Yokelson, Bernard J., undated; cuid2413; 11657 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Yokelson, Marshall V., undated; cuid2414; 11658 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Yoon, Lisa, undated; cuid2415; 13187 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Youla, Dante C., undated; cuid2416; 11659 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Young, Morris, undated; cuid2417; 11660 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Yousoufian, Hrant H., undated; cuid2418; 11661 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Yuan, [J.], undated; cuid2419; 11662 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Yusim, Galina, undated; cuid2420; 11663 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Z, 11664
  - Zabar, Zivan, circa 1995; cuid2421; 11665 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Zach, Theodore A., 1955; cuid2422; 11666 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Zahner, [Richard ?], undated; cuid2423; 11667 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Zauderer, Erich, undated; cuid2424; 11668 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Zeldin, Martin, undated; cuid2425; 11669 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Zerban, Alexander H., undated; cuid2426; 11670 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Zhang, GaoYong, undated; cuid2427; 11671 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Ziegler, Edward, 1993; cuid2428; 11672 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Ziegler, Henry Martin, 1956; cuid2429; 11673 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Ziehl, Charles, undated; cuid2430; 11674 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Zienkowicz, J.J., 1943; cuid2431; 11675 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Ziv, Nina, undated; cuid2432; 11676 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Zito, Frederick A., undated; cuid2433; 11677 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Zitzmann, Frank Richard, 1956; cuid2434; 11678 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Zlatanova, Jordana, undated; cuid2435; 11679 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Zucker, Frederic E., circa 1980; cuid2436; 11680 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Zuckerman, Robert, undated; cuid2437; 11681 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Zurawsky, Walter, undated; cuid2438; 11682 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Zworykin, Vladimir K., undated; cuid2439; 11683 (Box 9, Folder 121)
- Miscellaneous, 11684
  - Unknown- Polytechnic Fellows, undated; cuid2440; 11685 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2441; 11686 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2442; 11687 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2443; 14823 (Box 9, Folder 125)